puzzleanddragonsforum.com 2014-11-01

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Puzzle & Dragons Forum uses and protects any information that you provide, whilst using Puzzle & Dragons Forum products and services. This includes, but is not limited to, PuzzleAndDragonsForum.com and any associated websites and sub-domains.

Puzzle & Dragons Forum is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any information provided by you to Puzzle & Dragons Forum, by which you can be identified, will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

Puzzle & Dragons Forum may change this policy as and when necessary. It is your responsibility to check this privacy policy periodically to ensure you agree with any changes.

Security

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to Puzzle & Dragons Forum is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

How we use cookies and IP addresses  

PuzzleAndDragonsForum.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, use small text files, called cookies, to store information in your web browser. The information stored may include preferences, session identification, HTTP information, and IP address.

You can set your browser to not receive cookies, but this may limit your ability to use PuzzleAndDragonsForum.com and any associated websites and sub-domains.

IP addresses of computers used to visit PuzzleAndDragonsForum.com and any associated websites and sub-domains are stored in our database. This includes when first registering for an account, managing your account details, writing a private or public message or performing any other transaction which results in data being transferred to or from your computer and the website in question.

Your IP address is not visible to the public at any time.

Links to other websites  

PuzzleAndDragonsForum.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with Puzzle & Dragons Forum.

Puzzle & Dragons Forum has no control over any external websites therefore clicking any link which results in you visiting an external website will result in this privacy policy no longer applying and Puzzle & Dragons Forum cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites.

Controlling your personal information

Puzzle & Dragons Forum will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you security information, product updates, or other information pertaining to Puzzle & Dragons Forum, or your account.

If you discover any of the information Puzzle & Dragons Forum holds for you is incorrect or incomplete, that you are unable to change yourself, please contact us as soon as possible so the necessary changes can be made.  
~
